(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おめかし中...
Getting ready...
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heartbeats resound
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
うーっぱー！
Woo-pa!
覚えてるかな？ 最初の歌
Do you remember? That first song
あの日 声が震えていた
That day, my voice was trembling
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the today we grasped together
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
More and more and more and more, my accelerating heart
行くよ どこまでも
I'm going, wherever it leads
準備は OK？
Are you ready?
開け夢の扉を
Open the door to our dreams
1 2 3 キラメキライダー！
1 2 3 Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heartbeats resound
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディー
An unending melody
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
届いてるかな？ 私の声
Is it reaching you? My voice
届けたいのは君に笑顔
What I want to deliver to you is a smile
理想と遠さに悔しくて
Frustrated by the distance from my ideals
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Tightly, tightly, tightly, tightly, embracing everything
行こう どこまでも
Let's go, wherever it leads
準備は OK？
Are you ready?
進め希望の道を
Go forth on the path of hope
1 2 3 キラメキライダー！
1 2 3 Kirameki Rider!
好きな気持ち カラフルに飾られたいんだ
I want to be decorated colorfully with my feelings of love
最高の場所 最高のみんなと
At the best place with the best everyone
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not some illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart will be dyed in happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
Our overlapping harmonies
キラメキを纏って
Clad in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願いはわがままでもいいでしょ
Such a wish, it's okay even if it's selfish, right?
だって楽しすぎて止まらない 輝くステージで
Because it's just too much fun and I can't stop on this shining stage
もっとまわって　ずっと...
Keep spinning, more and more...
嬉しい　楽しい　愛しい　だけじゃ勝てない
Being happy, having fun, or being loved
isn't enough to win.
今も　今も　悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I still have my worries.
ここにいるよ　私ここにいるよ
I'm right here. I'm right here.
君と同じ世界を　見つめていくよ
I'll keep looking at the same world as you.
キラメキライダー！
Kira-Kira Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make this fresh excitement resonate.
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best of friends.
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me.
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ　みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you.
Let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ　きらめきに乗って
An endless melody, riding on the sparkle.
きらめきまとって
Wearing the sparkle...
Yeah!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
1曲目、『キラメキライダー！』でしたー！
The first song was 'Kira-Kira Rider'!
改めまして、こんねねー！
Once again, Kon-nene!
ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当の桃鈴ねねです！
I'm Momosuzu Nene from Hololive Gen 5,
in charge of orange!
本日、お誕生日だー！
Today is my birthday!
イエーイ！
Yay!
パチパチパチパチ... あ、緊張しすぎて発声間違えちゃったみんな。
(Claps) Ah, I was so nervous I messed up
my greeting.
どうしよう。あー、やばい。脇汗びっしり。
What should I do? Ah, this is bad.
My armpits are soaking wet.
あーー！ね、見て見てこの背景！
Ah! Hey, look, look at this background!
え、どう？いつものさ、ライブ背景とちょっと違うでしょ？
Well, what do you think? It's a bit different
from my usual live background, right?
これね、あの、根っこの人が、え、作ってくれました！ありがとう！
A Nekko (fan) actually made this for me!
Thank you!
放送終わったらね、あの、リツイートするのでよかったら、あの、作ってくれた人見に行ってください。
I'll retweet it after the stream, so please
go check out the creator if you like.
え、え、え、めっちゃいいでしょ？かっこよくない？
Eh, eh, eh, it's really good, right? Isn't it cool?
めっちゃかっこいいでしょ？あとこれ見て！
It's so cool, right? And look at this!
根っこもね、応援してる根っこもご用意してみたんで。うふふ。
I also prepared some cheering Nekko. Hehe.
というわけで今日は、7回目のねねのライブ枠、お誕生日枠に来てくれて、ありがとうございます！
Anyway, thank you for coming to my 7th live stream,
my birthday stream!
あー、緊張しすぎて無理！やばい！
Ah, I'm too nervous! This is bad!
うーー！緊張したー。
Ugh! I was so nervous.
すごいね、いろいろ準備して。今日はね、重大発表もあるから！
I've prepared a lot of things.
I have a major announcement today too!
最後まで見てほしい！最後まで、みんな、いい？
I want you to watch until the end!
Until the very end, okay everyone?
今日はお願いだから、あの、9時くらいまでね、時間ちょうだい。お願い、お願い、お願い...
Please give me your time until about 9 o'clock today.
Please, please, please...
はい、というわけで早速次は、え、2曲目に移っていきたいと思います。
Alright, so without further ado, let's move on
to the second song.
さあ、今日はお歌歌いに来たんでね、お、みんなに歌聴いてもらうんだ。みんな聴いてね！
I came here to sing today, so I'm going to
let everyone hear my songs. Please listen!
よろしく。じゃあさっきのステージに戻ろう。いーーー...ドン！
Thanks. Now, let's go back to that stage.
Ready... bam!
青空の下君を待った　風が吹いた正午
I waited for you under the blue sky,
at noon when the wind blew.
昼下がりもぬけの殻の燥ね
In the early afternoon, a hollow dryness, right?
これからどうなるんだろうね
I wonder what will happen now.
進め方を教わらないんだよ
We're not taught how to move forward.
君の目を見た　何も言えず僕は歩いた
I looked into your eyes.
Without saying anything, I walked on.
考えたってわからないし　青春なんてつまらないし
Thinking about it doesn't help,
and youth is just boring.
辞めたはずのピアノ　机を弾く癖が抜けないね
The piano I was supposed to have quit—
the habit of playing on the desk remains.
将来何してるだろうね　音楽はしてないといいね
I wonder what I'll be doing in the future.
I hope I'm not doing music.
困らないでよ
Don't look so troubled.
心の中に一つ線を引いても
Even if I draw a line in my heart,
どうしても消えなかった　今更なんだからもう
it just wouldn't disappear.
It's too late for that now, anyway.
もういらないな
I don't need it anymore.
間違ってるんだよ　わかってないよ　あんたら人間も
You're all wrong. You don't understand,
either—not even you humans.
本当も愛も世界も狂った様だ、人生もどうでもいいよ
The truth, love, even the world seems to have gone mad, and my life doesn't matter anymore.
正しいかどうか知りたいのらって防衛本能だ
Wanting to know if it's right or not is just a self-defense instinct.
考えたんだ、あんたのせいだ
I thought about it, and it's all your fault.
あ、この曲好き！
Ah, I love this song!
Ah, Ah, Ah...
考えたって分かんないが、本当に年老いたくないな
Even if I think about it, I don't know, but I really don't want to grow old.
いつか死んだって思うだけで、胸が空っぽになるんだ
Just the thought of dying someday makes my heart feel empty.
将来何してるだろうって、大人になったら分かったよ
I wondered what I'd be doing in the future, and now that I'm an adult, I know.
何もしてないさ
I'm not doing anything.
幸せな顔をした人が憎いのは
Why I hate people who look happy...
どう割り切ったらいいんだ
...how am I supposed to deal with that?
満たされない頭の奥の苦悩
The suffering deep within my unfulfilled mind...
化け物みたいな劣等感
...an inferiority complex like a monster.
間違ってないよ、あんたなんだ、あんたら人間だ
You're not wrong, it's you, you humans.
愛も救いも優しさも根拠がないなんて
Love, salvation, and kindness having no basis...
君が悪いよ、ラブソングなんかが歌いたいのらって防衛本能だ
...is your fault, wanting to sing love songs is just a self-defense instinct.
どうでもいいか、あんたのせいだ
Does it matter? It's all your fault.
考えたって分かんないし、生きてるだけでも苦しいし
Thinking about it doesn't help, and just living is painful.
音楽とかも乗っからないし、歌詞とか適当でもいいよ
I can't even get into the music, so whatever lyrics are fine.
どうでもいいんだ
It doesn't matter.
間違ってないだろ
It's not wrong, right?
間違ってないよな
It's not wrong, is it?
間違ってるんだよ、分かってるんだ、あんたら人間も
It's wrong, I know that, you humans too.
本当も愛も救いも優しさも人生も、どうでもいいんだ
The truth, love, salvation, kindness, even life, it doesn't matter.
正しい答えが言えないのらって防衛本能だ
Being unable to give the right answer is just a self-defense instinct.
どうでもいいや、あんたのせいだ
Whatever, it's all your fault.
Ah...
僕だって信念があった、今じゃゴミみたいな思い出だ
I had convictions once, too, but now they're just like trash memories.
何度でも君を書いた、売れることこそがどうでもよかったんだ
I wrote about you over and over, I didn't care about selling records.
本当だ、本当なんだ、昔はそうだった
It's true, it really is, it used to be like that.
だから僕は...
That's why I...
音楽を、辞めた
...quit music.
はい！というわけで、2曲目でした！
Yes! And that was the second song!
それでは続けて、3曲目お聴きください！
Now, please listen to the third song!
初披露の曲！おどるポンポコリン！
A first-time performance song! Odoru Ponpokorin!
タッタタラリラ
Tatta-tararira
なんでもかんでもみんな、おどりを踊っているよ
Everything and everyone is dancing a dance.
お鍋の中からボワっと、インチキおじさん登場
Poof, out of the pot appears the phony old man.
いつだってパンパン、忘れないエジソンはパンパン、えらい人
Always boom-boom, never forget Edison was a boom-boom, a great man.
そんなの常識
That's common sense.
タッタタラリラ、ピーヒャラピーヒャラ
Tatta-tararira, pee-hyara pee-hyara
パッパパラパ、ピーヒャラピーヒャラ
Pappa-parapa, pee-hyara pee-hyara
おへそがチラリ
A glimpse of the belly button.
タッタタラリラ、ピーヒャラピーヒャラ
Tatta-tararira, pee-hyara pee-hyara
パッパパラパ、ピーヒャラピーヒャラ
Pappa-parapa, pee-hyara pee-hyara
おどるポンポコリン、ピーヒャラピー
Dancing Ponpokorin, pee-hyara-pee.
おなかがへったよ
I'm hungry.
あの子もこの子もみんな、いそいで歩いているよ
That kid and this kid, everyone is walking in a hurry.
電信柱の陰から、お笑い芸人登場
From behind the telephone pole appears a comedian.
いつだってパンパン、迷わないキヨスクはパンパン、駅の中
Always boom-boom, never lost, the Kiosk is boom-boom, inside the station.
そんなの有名
That's famous.
タッタタラリラ、ピーヒャラピーヒャラ
Tatta-tararira, pee-hyara pee-hyara
パッパパラパ、ピーヒャラピーヒャラ
Pappa-parapa, pee-hyara pee-hyara
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ
Pi-hyara pi-hyara
ニンジンいらない
No carrots needed
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Pi-hyara pi-hyara pappa-parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ
Pi-hyara pi-hyara
おどるポンポコリン
Odoru Ponpokorin
ピーヒャラ ピー
Pi-hyara pi
ブタのプタロー
Putaro the pig
ねぇ〜
Nee~
な〜い！
Nai!
ありがとうございました。おどるポンポコリンでした！
Thank you very much. That was 'Odoru Ponpokorin'!
えっと、絶対みんなが知ってる曲にしようと思ってさ、今日。
Um, I thought I'd choose a song that everyone definitely knows today.
これだったらさすがにどの年代の人でもわかってもらえると思って選びました。
I chose this because I thought people of any age would recognize it.
え、どうだった？
Eh, how was it?
よかった。緩急めっちゃいい感じだった。本当によかった、狙い通り。
Good. The pace was really nice. I'm glad, just as I planned.
はい、ちょっとお水を飲んで休憩します。
Okay, I'm going to drink some water and take a break.
えっと、ちょっと緊張してコメント見る暇なかったからコメント見るぞ。
Um, I was a bit nervous and didn't have time to look at the comments, so I'll look now.
ふむふむふむ。温度差で風邪ひく。よかった。お水助かる。楽しめる曲。
Hmm hmm hmm. 'The temperature difference will give me a cold.' Good. 'Water helps.' 'Enjoyable song.'
この選曲は読めない。
I couldn't predict this song choice.
ね、でしょ？ もうねねはみんなに予想外を今日はお届けしようと思って。
See, right? Nene thought she'd deliver the unexpected to everyone today.
いい感じだったでしょ？ あの、背景切り替えるタイミングも、なんかまるでわざとみたいだったでしょ？ 間違えただけだよ。
It was good, right? Um, the timing of the background switch, it looked almost intentional, didn't it? I just made a mistake.
え、キュンとした？ 本当？ ああ嬉しい、よかった。ありがとう。
Eh, did your heart skip a beat? Really? Oh, I'm so happy. Thank you.
イェーイ、見てる、見てるよ、ありがとう。
Yay, I'm watching, I'm watching, thank you.
さあ、こっからはね、まだ、まだまだ初披露の曲ありますよ、みんな。
Now, from here, there are still, still more songs I'm performing for the first time, everyone.
ちょっとね、なるべくいろんな人に、いろんな世代の人に伝わる曲にしようと思って、練習してきて。
I practiced thinking I'd make them songs that reach as many people and as many generations as possible.
次もね、その曲だね。ちょっとね、次、ちょっと緊張なんだよね、ねね的には。
The next one is that kind of song too. Um, the next one, I'm a bit nervous, personally.
なかなかね、覚えるのが難しくて、大変だったけど。
It was quite difficult to memorize and was tough, but...
これはもう絶対にわかる。絶対に聞いたことある。なんかフルでは知らなくても、絶対に聞いたことある。
You'll definitely recognize this one. You've definitely heard it. Even if you don't know the full version, you've definitely heard it.
もうお誕生日ガールに、あの、ふさわしい曲、ということにしとくわ。
I'll just say it's a song suitable for a birthday girl.
あ、何回でも言う。ねね、お誕生日だから何回でも言うね。ハッピーバースデーねねち！ おめでとう、おめでとうねね！
Oh, I'll say it as many times as it takes. It's Nene's birthday, so I'll say it again and again. Happy Birthday Nenechi! Congratulations, congrats Nene!
あ、最後まで見て。お願い、お願い、最後まで見て。
Ah, watch until the end. Please, please watch until the end.
よし、じゃあ、次の曲行っちゃおうかな。じゃ、背景をね、こっちにしたいと思います。
Alright, then, shall we go to the next song? So, I'll change the background to this one.
じゃ、次の選曲もみんな、え、よかったらね、当ててみてください。何でしょうか。もう発表しちゃうけど。
So, everyone, please try to guess the next song choice too. What is it? I'm about to announce it though.
え、それでは、4曲目聞いてください。TOMORROW。
Um, well then, please listen to the fourth song. 'TOMORROW'.
涙の数だけ強くなれるよ
You can become stronger as much as you shed tears
アスファルトに咲く花のように
Like a flower blooming on the asphalt
見るものすべてにおびえないで
Don't be afraid of everything you see
明日は来るよ 君のために
Tomorrow will come for you
どうしてた、みんな？
How was everyone doing?
突然会いたいなんて
Suddenly saying you want to meet
...なんて
...and things like that.
夜更けに何があったの？
What happened late at night?
あわててジョークにしても
Even if you hurriedly turn it into a joke,
その笑顔が悲しい
that smile of yours is sad.
ビルの上にはほら月明かり
Look, there's moonlight above the buildings.
抱きしめてる想い出とか
If you cast aside things like the memories,
プライドとか捨てたらまた
or the pride you're holding onto,
いいことあるから
something good will happen again.
涙の数だけ強くなれるよ
You can become stronger as many times
as you shed tears,
アスファルトに咲く花のように
like a flower blooming in the asphalt.
見るものすべてにおびえないで
Don't be afraid of everything you see.
明日は来るよ君のために
Tomorrow will come for you.
季節を忘れるくらい
So much that you forget the seasons,
いろなことがあったけど
a lot of things have happened.
二人でただ歩いてる
We're just walking together,
この感じが愛おしい
and I find this feeling so precious.
頼りにしてるだけど時には
I rely on you, but sometimes,
夢の荷物放り投げて
throw away the baggage of your dreams.
泣いてもいいよ付き合うから
It's okay to cry, because I'll be with you.
カッコつけないで
Don't try to look cool.
涙の数だけ強くなろうよ
Let's become stronger as many times
as we shed tears,
風に揺れている花のように
like a flower swaying in the wind.
自分をそのまま信じていてね
Just believe in yourself as you are.
明日は来るよどんな時も
Tomorrow will come, no matter when.
涙の数だけ強くなれるよ
You can become stronger as many times
as you shed tears,
アスファルトに咲く花のように
like a flower blooming in the asphalt.
見るものすべてにおびえないで
Don't be afraid of everything you see.
明日は来るよ君のために
Tomorrow will come for you.
涙の数だけ強くなろうよ
Let's become stronger as many times
as we shed tears,
風に揺れている花のように
like a flower swaying in the wind.
自分をそのまま信じていてね
Just believe in yourself as you are.
明日は来るよどんな時も
Tomorrow will come, no matter when.
明日は来るよ君のために
Tomorrow will come for you.
ありがとうございました！「TOMORROW」でした！
Thank you very much! That was 'TOMORROW'!
ねえ、どうだった？岡本真夜さんの曲「TOMORROW」でした！
Hey, how was it? That was Mayo Okamoto's song,
'TOMORROW'!
いや、みんなこれならね、知ってるんじゃないかなと思って。
サビだけねねねも最初知ってたんだけど、
No, I thought everyone would probably know this one.
I only knew the chorus at first,
今回フルで歌おうと思って、あの、曲を買ってね、聴いたんだけど、
すごい良い曲だった。びっくりした。
but I decided to sing the full version this time,
so I bought the song and listened to it, and it was a really great song. I was surprised.
今まではなんか、その、テレビでなんとなくサビだけ聴いて
頭に入れてたんだけど、
Until now, I'd just kind of heard the chorus on TV
and remembered it,
歌詞を見ながらね、歌詞を、あの、聞きながら見て聴いて、
実際に歌ってみたら、もうハチャメチャエモソングで、
but while looking at the lyrics and listening to them,
actually singing it, it's such an incredibly emotional song,
めちゃくちゃ良い曲でびっくりした。
I was shocked by how good a song it is.
あー、めっちゃ、もうなんか、半泣きになるね、なんか。
涙腺、涙腺に来る曲だった、とっても。
Ah, it's so... it makes me almost want to cry.
It's a song that really hits you right in the tear ducts.
歌っててね、すごい、あの、なんだろう、明るくもなるし、
なんかちょっと切なくもなる、みたいな。
Singing it, it's really... how should I say,
it makes you feel bright, but also a bit bittersweet.
そんな曲だった気がする。これはね、また、また歌っていきたい。
このね、あの、年代の曲っていうの、この、あの、ちょっと...
That's the kind of song I felt it was.
I want to sing this one again. Songs from this era, you know, this... a bit...
ねねよりは上の年代の曲なんだけど...
It's a song from a generation older than me, but...
この年代の曲たちもめちゃくちゃ良い曲たちが多くて、
there are so many great songs from that era,
なんか今回その選ぶにあたって何個か迷った曲がまだあって、
and there were a few others I was torn between when choosing this time,
いつか披露できるようにちょっと練習をしていきたいと思っております。
so I'd like to practice them so I can perform them someday.
うー...
Uhh...
緊張した！この曲全然終わらなくて、本当難しくてなんか...
I was so nervous! This song wouldn't end, it was so hard...
緊張したー。今日緊張したしか言ってない。
I'm so nervous. I've said nothing but "I'm nervous" today.
お水飲みます。
I'm going to drink some water.
いつか聞かせて、任せな、いつかね！
"Sing it for us someday." Leave it to me, someday!
リクエストも募集してますので、なんかいい曲など...
I'm also taking requests, so if you have any good songs...
歌ってほしい曲とかあったら、ねねにわかるように書いといてください！
...or songs you want me to sing, please write them down so I can see them!
いやあるよ、まだあるよ、今日はね、初披露の曲まだあります。
Wait, there's more. There's still more. I have more songs to perform for the first time today.
緊張するな。次は、あの...
I'm getting nervous. Next is...
「お願いマッスル」の時に、ねねのセルフ合いの手がすごく好評で嬉しかったから、
Since Nene's self-call-and-response in "Onegai Muscle" was so well-received and made me happy,
今回もちょっとセルフ合いの手を入れて1曲歌ってみたいと思っております！
I'd like to try singing another song with self-call-and-response this time!
というわけで次の曲行きましょう！
So, let's move on to the next song!
お誕生日の、お誕生日ガールのねねが楽しく歌う、楽しい曲！
A fun song, sung fun-ly by the birthday girl, Nene!
移動しよう。ぺい！
Let's move. Pei!
それでは、次の曲聞いてください。
Now, please listen to the next song.
アドレナリン！
Adrenaline!
うぉー！
Whoa!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
単純な言葉　重ねてゆく
Simple words keep piling up
もっと心は素直で
With a more honest heart
なんでもないようなその笑顔が
That casual smile of yours
明日を照らす光に
Becomes the light that shines on tomorrow
ずっと気付いていたんだって
I'd always known it
この手に抱えていたんだって
That I'd been holding it in my hands
弾けたスマイル　流した答えが今
A bursting smile, the answer I shed is now...
そっと　きっと　願い込めた
...softly, surely, filled with a wish
ずっと回る回る夢の中で
Inside a dream that keeps spinning and spinning
繰り返し君と踊った
I danced with you over and over again
揺れる景色　道は続く
The swaying scenery, the road continues
通り過ぎる風に吹かれ
Blown by the passing wind
何度も越えて行けるから境界線
I can cross the boundary line again and again
雲かき分け手を伸ばした
I pushed aside the clouds and reached out my hand
涙は今　浮かぶ空に預けて
Entrusting my tears to the floating sky now
走り出すの
I'll start running
並んで見つけた
Found them side-by-side
輝く光を手に
With the shining light in my hands
うぉー！
Whoa!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
問題はいつも自分次第さ
The problem is always up to you
未来を選んで
Choose your future
こんがらがった糸解いたら
Once you untangle the tangled threads
思いのまま進もう
Let's move forward as we wish
毎日冒険なんだって
Every day is an adventure
奇跡は無限大なんだって
Miracles are infinite
高鳴る思い　羅針盤のように今
These throbbing feelings, like a compass now...
そっと　きっと　導いてく
...softly, surely, will guide us
そうだ巡る巡る波に乗って
That's right, riding the waves that go round and round
風任せ君と笑った
I laughed with you, left to the wind
予想外は　いつだって大歓迎
The unexpected is always more than welcome
間違いや失敗も楽しんで
Enjoying mistakes and failures too
一歩踏み出したら見えた可能性
The possibilities I saw when I took a step forward
行き止まりの風　壊して
Breaking the dead-end wind
まだ知らない世界　君と一緒なら
A world I don't know yet, if I'm with you...
怖くないよ
...I'm not afraid
ワクワクしている
I'm getting excited
今が一番大好き
I love "now" the most
イェイ！イェイ！イェイ！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai!
うー、イェイ！
Uhh, yay!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai!
イェイ！イェイ！イェイ！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
うぉー！よっしゃー！
Whoa! Yossha!
大股で行こう
Let's take big steps forward
大丈夫
It's okay
心配ない
No need to worry
描いたもの全部叶えるよ
I'll make everything I've imagined come true
ずっと回る回る夢の中で
Always spinning and spinning inside a dream
繰り返す君と踊った
I danced with you over and over
いつか君と約束した
A promise I once made with you
願いの架け橋を渡って
Crossing the bridge of wishes
何度も越えてゆけるから
Because we can overcome anything
境界線
The boundary line
雲かき分けて手を伸ばした
Pushing aside the clouds and reaching out
涙は今浮かぶ空に預けて
Leaving my tears to the sky above
走り出すの
I'll start running
並んで見つけた
We found it together
輝く光を手に
With a shining light in our hands
ワクワクしている
I'm so excited
今が一番大好き
I love this moment the most
ふぉーーー！
Wooo!
続いてそのまま次の曲お聞きください。
Next, please listen to the next song right away.
さよならメモリーズ。
Sayonara Memories.
桜が咲くよ
The cherry blossoms are blooming
見慣れたいつもの坂道に
On the familiar slope we always take
お別れを
Saying our goodbyes
3月でね、卒業シーズンだから
It's March, so it's graduation season.
いま卒業ソングも歌っておこうと思って選びました。
I chose this song because I wanted to sing a graduation song now.
聴いててね！
Please listen!
ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai!
泣いて笑ったあの日々
Those days when we cried and laughed
なんだか昨日のことのよう
It feels like it was just yesterday
この道はそう未来へ続く道
This path, yes, it's the path that leads to the future
そんな気がしたの
That's how I felt
例年より早い開花予想を
The blooming forecast was earlier than usual
君は嬉しがってた
And you were happy about it
私は笑って「そうだね」と言った
I laughed and said, "You're right"
あと少ししたらもうここには戻れないのに
Even though soon we won't be able to return here anymore
言葉じゃうまく言えない思いを
Feelings that I can't quite put into words
君に打ち明けるとしたらなんて
If I were to confess them to you, what should I...
伝えよう 最初で最後
...say? This is the first and last time
いつか一緒に帰った道は
The path we once walked home together on
私にとって特別な思い出
Is a special memory for me
忘れないよ
I won't forget
さよならメモリーズ
Goodbye memories
春が来たらそれぞれの道を
When spring comes, we'll go our separate ways
また会える日を願って
Wishing for the day we meet again
「さよなら」小さくつぶやいた
I softly whispered, "Goodbye"
空はあの日と変わらず青くて
The sky is as blue as it was that day
だからちょっと泣けた
That's why I cried a little
わざと遠回りしたの
I purposely took the long way around
少しでも長く君の隣にいたくて
Because I wanted to be by your side for just a little longer
私はおどけて「間違えた」と言った
I joked and said, "I took the wrong turn"
君は笑う その顔が眩しくて目をそらした
You laughed; your face was so radiant that I looked away
言葉じゃうまく言えない思いを
Feelings that I can't quite put into words
胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
I walked this path with them held close to my heart
覚えてる あの時君は
I remember... at that time, you...
私の名前を呼んでくれた
You called my name
二人 夕暮れの帰り道で
The two of us on the way home at dusk
忘れないよ
I won't forget
さよならメモリーズ
Goodbye Memories
出会えたこと
For having met you
感謝してる
I'm thankful
初めて見た 満開の桜
The first time I saw the cherry blossoms in full bloom
あれからどれくらい
I wonder how much
変われたんだろう
I've changed since then
ひと目見た時に思ったんだ
The moment I laid eyes on you, I thought
この人のこと好きになりそうって
"I think I'm going to fall for this person"
なんでかな わかんないよ
I don't know why
それからの毎日
Since then, every day
とても楽しくて
Has been so much fun
だけど同じくらい
But just as much
辛かったんだ
It was also painful
ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ
I'm sorry, I can't quite say it right
だから私 君となんていうか
So I... with you, how should I put it...
今のまま さよならしたくないの
I don't want to say goodbye just like this
友達のままじゃ もう嫌なの
I don't want to stay just friends anymore
言おうと思ってた
I've been meaning to tell you
私君の 君のことずっと
That I... for you...
ずっと前から
For a long time now...
好きでした
I've loved you
やっと言えた
I finally said it
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
adrenalineとさよならメモリーズ、
That was 'adrenaline' and 'Sayonara Memories',
2曲連続でお聴きいただきました
two songs performed back-to-back.
えっと、どうだった？
So, how was it?
どうだった？
How was it?
ちょっとさよならメモリーズは結構、結構練習したから、
I practiced 'Sayonara Memories' quite a bit,
あの、いい感じにみんなの耳に聴こえてたらいいなと思っております。
so I hope it sounded good to everyone.
やばすぎ？やばすぎか。やばすぎ嬉しいな、ありがとう。
Too amazing? Really? That makes me so happy, thank you.
よし。
Alright.
というわけで、えっとここからは、えっとまだまだ歌ってまいりたいのですが、
With that, I'd like to keep singing more, but...
その前に、ねねから重大発表の前に、お知らせがあります！
Before the major announcement, I have some news!
さてさて、ちょっとお知らせ、させてもろてええかな？
Now then, may I share some news with you?
もうちょっといい子に喋ろうかな。
I should probably speak more properly.
よし。
Okay.
というわけで、ちょっと明るい方のステージへ、ん？このままいくかな？よし。
So, should I move to the brighter stage? Or stay here? Let's stay.
お誕生日といえば！
Speaking of birthdays!
もうねねの概要欄を見て、ちょっと察してる人もいるかもしれないのですが、
Some of you might have already guessed by looking at my description,
ねねち初の！えっと公式ソログッズ、出ます！
Nenechi's first official solo merchandise is coming out!
ドーン！
BAM!
桃鈴ねね 誕生記念2021
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Celebration 2021
桃鈴ねね誕生日記念2021！イェーイ！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Celebration 2021! Yay!
内容は、ボイスのボイスとグッズ、
The contents are voices and goods,
あとざらま先生描き下ろしの、アクリルパネルと
an acrylic panel illustrated by Zarama-sensei,
ねねプロの社章ピンバッジと、ねねプロの社員カード！
a NenePro company pin, and a NenePro employee ID card!
なんと、こちらがですね、ですね、
And these... check them out...
こちらがですね、ちょっと見てほしい、
I want you to see these,
まずアクリルパネルから見てもらおうかな。
first, let's look at the acrylic panel.
じゃあ、見てみて！
Okay, look!
ああ！可愛い！
Aah! It's so cute!
西沢5㍉先生描き下ろし
箔押しメッセージ入りアクリルパネル
Illustration by Nishizawa 5mm
Acrylic panel with foil-stamped message
なんとあの箔押しメッセージ入りのアクリルパネル！
An acrylic panel with a foil-stamped message!
...直筆メッセージ入りのアクリルパネル。
...acrylic panel with a handwritten message.
ねねの直筆文字入りのアクリルパネル。
An acrylic panel with my handwritten message.
そして、えー、えっとね、グッズの方が...
And, uh, well, about the merchandise...
ドン！
Ta-da!
「ねねプロ」の社員ピンバッジと「ねねプロ」の社員カードが出ます。
The "Nene Pro" employee pin badge and employee card are coming out.
社員ピンバッジ見て。これ、あの...
Look at the employee pin badge. This is, uh...
「ねねプロダクション」の、あの、公式ロゴが出来上がりました。「ね」！
The official logo for "Nene Production" is finished. "Ne"!
「ね」って書いてるやつと、社員カードはね、なんと...
The one with "Ne" on it, and the employee card, surprisingly...
Husbandsナンバー入り！シリアルナンバーが入ります！
Includes a Husbands number! It will have a serial number!
みんなね、今まで勝手にナンバー名乗ってたけど...
Everyone has been calling themselves numbers on their own until now...
とうとう、あの、公式的に番号が配られることになりました！
...but finally, numbers will be officially distributed!
イエーイ！
Yay!
じゃ、社員証なんだけど、あの、Husbandsナンバーって書いてあるのね。ちょっとアップで見たい。
Now, about the employee ID card, it says "Husbands Number" on it. Let's take a closer look.
ほら見て！Husbandsナンバー入ります。
See! It includes a Husbands number.
そしてなんと、裏面は、ねねが提出物の嵐に追われていた時、何を書いていたのかと言うと...
And surprisingly, on the back... what was Nene writing while she was swamped with a storm of submissions?
社員証の裏にはなんとねねの、オリジナルの書き下ろしのイラストとメッセージ！
On the back of the ID card is Nene's original illustration and message!
そしてね、この裏面のデザインね、なんとねねがしました。
And Nene designed the back of the card herself!
名前書くところ書いたので、みんなにそれぞれの名前を書いて持ち歩いてほしい！
I made a space for you to write your names, so I want everyone to carry it with them!
イエーイ！
Yay!
そんでもって、そんでもって、全部セットっていうのがございまして...
And then, and then, there's an all-in-one set...
全部、全部にすると...
If you get everything...
はい！グッズ＆ボイス全部セットの特典は、なんとねねの直筆サイン入り...
Yes! The bonus for the merch & voice all-in-one set is a handwritten signature from Nene!
頑張って書く！西沢5㍉先生描き下ろしイラストのポストカード、プラス特典ボイス！
I'll do my best to sign them! It's a postcard by Nishizawa 5mm-sensei, plus a bonus voice!
見て、ポストカードこれ、見て見て見て見て見て！
Look at this postcard, look look look look!
ほら！みんなの腕が生えてるー！
Look! Everyone's arms are growing!
えー！いい！ねね、なでなでされてんだけど！
Whoa! Nice! Nene is getting headpats!
ねね、なでなでされてんだけど！ライブ前のねねを応援してくれているみんなをね...
Nene is getting headpats! It's an image of everyone supporting me before the live...
イメージで、そんな感じにしてみました。
...that's how I designed it.
(笑) みんなね、ここにコラして自分の写真撮って自分でコラージュしてさ...
(Laughs) Everyone, collage your own photo here and...
まるで自分がなでなでしてるみたいな感じでやってほしい！
...make it look like you're the one giving me headpats!
さあ、グッズの紹介をしたところで...
Now, with the merchandise introduction finished...
カートオープンが45分になります。あと2分で...
The shop will open at 45 minutes past. In 2 minutes...
カートオープンで、販売開始が21時となりますので...
The shop will open and sales will start at 21:00...
21時まではねねの配信見るでしょ、みんな。見て、見て、見てってね。
...so everyone will watch Nene's stream until 21:00, right? Watch it, watch it.
はい。これ隅っこ置いとこうかな。
Okay. I'll put this in the corner.
隅っこ置いとこうかな。置いとこう。
I'll put it in the corner. There.
はい、というわけで、このテンションぶち上げのところで...
Alright, with this high energy...
次も初披露の曲聴いてもらいたいと思います。
I'd like you to hear the next song, which is also a first performance.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
「はるもどき」。
"Harumodoki".
探しに行くんだ そこへ
I'm going to look for it, over there.
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
まだここから重大発表あるからみんな どこも行かないで
There are still major announcements coming up, so don't go anywhere, everyone!
空を埋め 構成した手入れ
Filling the sky, a reconstructed arrangement,
正しいはずなのに
Even though it's supposed to be correct,
ひらりひら 空回り
Fluttering and spinning in place.
未来はいびつで わずかな亀裂から
The future is distorted, and through a tiny crack,
いくらでもよれて 理想から逸れてゆくんだ
It can twist as much as it wants, straying from the ideal.
ぬるま湯がずっと 冷めてゆく音がしてた
I could hear the sound of the lukewarm water gradually cooling down.
道を変えるのなら
If I'm going to change my path,
今なんだ 壊れレプリカは いらない
It's now. I don't need a broken replica.
本物と呼べるものだけでいい
Only what I can call genuine will do.
探しに行くんだ そこへ
I'm going to look for it, over there.
でもそれは よくできた フェアリーテイルみたい
But that was like a well-crafted fairy tale.
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
答えの消えた クラウンを見つめる
Gazing at a crown from which the answer has vanished
埋めたはずなのに どうしてもわからない
I should have buried it, but I just don't understand
綺麗な花は 大事に育てても
Even if you carefully nurture a beautiful flower
遠慮ない土足で 簡単に踏みにじられた
It was easily trampled by inconsiderate muddy feet
降り積もる白に
In the accumulating white
小さな芽 覆われてく
The small sprouts are being covered
遠い 遠い 春は
The distant, distant spring...
雪の下 見えないものは どうしても
The things you can't see under the snow, no matter what
記憶から薄れてしまうんだ
They end up fading from memory
探しに行く場所さえも
Even the places to go looking for them
見失う僕たちは 気づかず芽を踏む
We, who have lost sight, step on the sprouts without realizing
思い出を頼りに 形作ってた花は すぐ枯れた
The flowers I formed by relying on memories withered quickly
足元には気づかずに
Without noticing what was at my feet
本物と呼べる場所を
A place that can be called real
探しに行くのは きっと
Going out to find it is surely...
今なんだ こんなレプリカはいらない
It's now; I don't need a replica like this
本物と呼べるものだけでいい
Only things that can be called real are enough
探しに行くから 君を
Because I'm going out to find you
ありがとう 小さな芽 見つけてくれたこと
Thank you for finding the small sprout
君は呟いた
You whispered
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
イェーーーーイ！
Yeeeaaaaah!
さて皆様、場所移動してねねピュ〜ン！
Well everyone, moving to a new spot, Nene-pyun!
ここからはねねの重大発表の時間です！イェ〜イ！
From here, it's time for Nene's major announcement! Yay!
え、なんと何と、ここからは、この曲は切り抜き禁止になります！
Eh, what what, from here on, this song will be prohibited from being clipped!
え、何で何で？
Eh, why why?
この曲は切り抜き禁止です！
Clipping this song is prohibited!
あー、水も飲んで... ちょっと飲ませて。
Ah, let me drink some water... let me drink a bit.
みんなが、え、重大発表ね、すごい楽しみにしてくれてて...
Everyone has been, uh, really looking forward to the major announcement...
いろんなね、予想をTwitterでしてくれたりしてるのを見て...
Seeing you all make various predictions on Twitter...
すごい今から発表できるのが、とっても、とっても... 楽しみ！
I'm so, so... looking forward to being able to announce it now!
50万人おめでとう？え、50万人いったの？！
Congrats on 500k? Eh, did I reach 500k?!
あーーー！！ハーフミリオンだ！お誕生日に記念日被った！
AAAAAA!! It's half a million! My milestone overlapped with my birthday!
え、嬉しすぎ！無理無理無理！どうしよう！テンション爆上げで重大発表できそう。
Eh, I'm too happy! No way! What should I do! I think I can make the announcement with high tension.
それでは、え、ねねからの今日の重大発表...
Well then, uh, today's major announcement from Nene...
発表します！3！2！1！ドーン！
I'm announcing it! 3! 2! 1! Boom!
ね、桃鈴ねね1stシングル「ねねねねねねねね！大爆走」オリジナル曲発表！イェ〜イ！
Nene's, Momosuzu Nene's 1st single 'Nenenenenenene Daibakusou' original song announcement! Yay!
桃鈴ねね 1stシングル「ねねねねねねねね!大爆走」
2021/3/3 0:00〜 配信開始！
Momosuzu Nene 1st Single 'Nenenenenenene Daibakusou'
Distribution starts 2021/3/3 0:00~
桃鈴ねね 1stシングル
ねねねねねねねね！大爆走
Momosuzu Nene 1st Single
Nene-nene-nene-nene! Daibakuso
ねねのファーストシングル、ヒゲドライバーさんにお願いしました！
I asked Hige Driver to compose my first single!
あーーー！
Aaaaah!
なんと今日のね、日付が変わった、え、3月3日0時から配信開始になります！
And it starts streaming today as the date changes, from 0:00 on March 3rd!
なんとジャケットは、ねねの描きおろし！
And the jacket art was drawn by me!
頑張って描いた！
I worked hard on it!
ロゴもねねが作った！
I made the logo too!
え、なんで切り抜き禁止かと言うと...
As for why clipping is prohibited...
今からここで初発表、生歌でさせてもらうんですけど、まだMVがね、え、完成してなくて...
I'm doing the premiere here and singing it live, but the MV isn't finished yet...
え、ちょっとそれまでは切り抜きを禁止にしてMVを待ってもらいたい、そんな意向で...
Until then, I want to prohibit clipping and have you wait for the MV. That's my intention...
今回切り抜き禁止にさせていただきました！
So I've made clipping prohibited this time!
この曲は切り抜き禁止です！
Clipping is prohibited for this song!
いいわ、こんなんまで作っちゃって。フォトショ触れるようになってからこんなんまで作っちゃってねね。
It's great, I even made this. Since I learned Photoshop, I've been making things like this.
さあ、え、どんな曲だと思う？どんな曲だと思う？
Now, what kind of song do you think it is?
聴いてほしい。合いの手が入ってるんだけど、合いの手はね、5期生の皆にお願いしました！
I want you to hear it. It has back-up vocals, and I asked all the 5th gen members to do them!
皆ありがとう！
Thanks everyone!
すごいね、あの、タイトなスケジュールだったんだけど、皆ね、もうね、二つ返事で「いいよ」って言ってくれて...
It was a really tight schedule, but everyone agreed immediately, saying "Sure!"...
すごい、すごい、いい曲になりました！もう嬉しすぎ！
It turned into such a great song! I'm so happy!
ずっとね準備してて、もう発表がね、楽しみで楽しみで、もうしょうがなくって...
I've been preparing for so long, I couldn't wait for this announcement...
もう今日ここで、あの、歌えるのがもう本当に楽しみ！
I'm really excited to be able to sing it here today!
ちょっともうさ、感極まっちゃって泣きそうなんだけど、なるべくCD音源に近く歌えるように頑張りますので...
I'm getting so emotional I feel like crying, but I'll do my best to sing it as close to the CD quality as possible...
えっと、曲をぜひ買ってほしいんですけど、もし買えないよって人はねねのこの枠で、ここで聴いて、いっぱい覚えてほしい。
I'd love for you to buy the song, but if you can't, please listen to it here in this stream and learn the lyrics.
5期生の皆に聴いてもらったら、すっごい耳に残るって言ってもらえたから、皆の耳にも残ってもらえるように頑張って歌いたいと思います！
The other 5th gen members told me it's really catchy, so I'll do my best to sing it so it sticks in your head too!
はー、緊張、緊張する...
Phew, I'm so nervous...
皆が曲を買ってくれたお金はねねが次のオリジナル曲を作るための費用にしますので...
The money from your purchases will go towards the costs of making my next original song...
ねねが今後もアイドル目指して活動続けていけるように、よかったら、曲は買ってほしいなっていうねねからのお願いです！
So please buy the song so I can keep working towards my goal of being an idol. That's my request!
というわけで歌っていきましょうか！ねねねねねねねね！大爆走！
All right, shall we sing? Nene-nene-nene-nene! Daibakuso!
あ、セトリに出ちゃった！
Oh, it showed up on the setlist!
はー、緊張する...
Phew, so nervous...
それでは聴いてください！ねねの初のオリジナル曲！
Now, please listen! My very first original song!
なななな　ななじゃなくて
Na-na-na-na, it's not Nana
にににに　ににじゃなくて
Ni-ni-ni-ni, it's not Nini
ぬぬぬぬ　ぬぬじゃなくて
Nu-nu-nu-nu, it's not Nunu
のののの　ののじゃなくて
No-no-no-no, it's not Nono
おーー　ねね！
Ohhh, Nene!
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょよいしょよいしょよいしょ！
Yoisho yoisho yoisho yoisho!
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょよいしょよいしょよいしょ　こんねね！
Yoisho yoisho yoisho yoisho, Kon-nene!
ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当　桃鈴ねねです
Hololive 5th Gen Orange, Momosuzu Nene here!
異世界から来ました　アイドル志望の新人VTuber
A rookie VTuber from another world aspiring to be an idol!
まあとにかく明るく行きましょ　ちょっとくらい緊張したって滑ったって
Anyway, let's keep it bright, even if I'm nervous or bomb a bit!
うわーって感じでさ、とりゃーってやっていこう
With a "Waa!" and a "Toryaa!", let's just go!
諦めの悪さは長所だよねねねねねねねね...
My stubbornness is my best trait, right, Ne-ne-ne-ne...
あんなこともあったけど　悔しいこともあったけど
There were times like that, there were frustrating times too
大丈夫、今日もっかりおめかしして　いつかきっとスーパーねねち
It's okay, I'll dress up properly again today, one day for sure, I'll be Super Nenechi
ついてきてねねねねねねねね...
Follow me, ne-ne-ne-ne...
全力で行こうぜ　前回で行こうぜ
Let's go at full power, let's go at full throttle
思い切りやればなんとかなるよ
If you give it your all, it'll work out somehow
ポンコツだっていい　誤字ったっていい
It's okay to be a klutz, it's okay to have typos
ただ駆け抜けていこうよ　ねねねねね！
Let's just keep running through, Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne!
この曲は切り抜き禁止です！
Clipping this song is prohibited!
ねねねねねねねね！大爆走！
Nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen! Daibakuso!
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho.
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho.
野菜ジュースと炭酸とお菓子揃えて準備OK！
Veggie juice, soda, and snacks ready, I'm all set!
でも朝は苦手、夜も苦手、
But I'm bad with mornings and bad with nights,
やっぱり睡眠って大事だよね。
Sleep really is important, isn't it?
ねねねねねねねね！
Nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen!
たくさんの人に愛されちゃい、
I want to be loved by lots of people,
チュッチュッチュ！チュッチュッチュ！
Chu chu chu! Chu chu chu!
大好きなみんなに愛されちゃい、
I want to be loved by everyone I love,
チュッチュッチュ！チュッチュッチュ！
Chu chu chu! Chu chu chu!
そしたらなるんだハイパーねねち！
And then I'll become Hyper Nenechi!
やっちゃって！
Let's do this!
ねねねねねねねね！ねねねねねねねね！
Nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen! (x2)
全力で行こうぜ！全開で行こうぜ！
Let's go at full power! Let's go at full throttle!
歌は誰にも負けたくないんだ。
I don't want to lose to anyone when it comes to singing.
大きな声で、朝の前に、
In a loud voice, before the morning comes,
ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね！
I'm gonna go to the restroom for a bit!
レッツラブタイム！
Let's love time!
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho.
ねね！
Nene!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho.
なななな、ななじゃなくて！
Na-na-na-na, it's not "Na"!
にににに、ににじゃなくて！
Ni-ni-ni-ni, it's not "Ni"!
ぬぬぬぬ、ぬぬじゃなくて！
Nu-nu-nu-nu, it's not "Nu"!
のののの、ののじゃなくて！
No-no-no-no, it's not "No"!
ただいま！
I'm back!
最後にねねねねねねねね！ねねねねねねねね！
Finally, Nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen! (x2)
ねねねねねねねね！ねねねねねねねね！
Nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen-nen! (x2)
全力で行こうぜ！全開で行こうぜ！
Let's go at full power! Let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやればなんとかなるよ。
If you give it your all, things will work out.
ポンコツだっていい、ドジだっていい。
It's okay to be a klutz, it's okay to be clumsy.
ただ駆け抜けていこうぜ、ねねねねね！
Let's just keep running through, nen-nen-nen-nen-ne!
大爆走！
Daibakuso!
それじゃあまたねね！
Well then, see you later-nene!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
このあと23時50分からは、
Starting from 23:50 tonight,
曲発売までカウントダウンの枠取りたいと思います。
I'm planning to do a countdown stream until the song is released.
みんな見に来てね！
Everyone, please come and watch!
明日はなんと！空先輩の新装配信！
Tomorrow is, amazingly, Sora-senpai's new outfit stream!
みんなで見に行こう！
Let's all go and watch it together!